

## **PROFILE**

I offer 4 years of experience in development, currently working as a Software Engineer in Coventry UK.

I am open and available for new opportunities in Switzerland. My goal is to keep growing my career specifically as a Full-Stack Software Engineer.

Programming is my passion, I am highly motivated, focused, with a lot of will to keep learning.

I believe in hard work, desire and constant dedication.

# **CONTACT**

PHONE:

+44 7448719858

FMAII:

atanasskambitovv@gmail.com

#### **SOCIAL MEDIA**

GitHub:

https://github.com/NASOKILA

LinkedIn:

https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100004882428094

Facebook:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/atanas-

kambitov-a69528162

# ATANAS KAMBITOV

# **Software Engineer**

# **EDUCATION**

South-West University "Neofit Rilski" 15/09/2014 - 25/05/2017 Bachelor degree of Informatics.

## Private Software University (SoftUni)

05/12/2016 - 21/12/2018

Professionally graduated and qualified C# and JavaScript developer.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Sainsbury's Store Support Centre | Software Engineer

03/12/2018 - Now

Design and build multiple integration systems and scaled dockerised micro services with several programming and clouding technologies. I put in more hours, desire, and dedication in order to perform and quickly deliver quality code.

#### SoftUni | Junior Web Developer

05/12/2016 - 21/12/2018

Create, host and maintain backend API's, databases and frontend apps. I had the opportunity to work on many projects with deferent technologies, languages and frameworks.

# Paolo Pavia | Prestashop & WordPress Developer

11/05/2015 - 19/05/2016

Develop, support and refactor websites related to shopping, advertisement and promotion.

I was able to learn faster and perform better than any other colleague.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Agile Methodologies | Azure DevOps | Kubernetes | GitHub | Docker Microservices | REST | .NET Core | .Net Framework | React.js Redux | Angular.js 2+ | Typescript | Vue.js | JavaScript | Mongo DB SQL | HTML5 & CSS3 | Less & Sass | Bootstrap | Node.js & Express

# PERSONAL PROJECTS

.Net Core:

https://aithub.com/NASOKILA/Tanay-Restaurant

Angular.js 2+:

https://nasokila.github.io/comix-shop/

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Portfolio-Projects/tree/comix-shop

React.js:

https://nasokila.github.io/house-shop/

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Portfolio-Projects/tree/house-shop